(Raj:)-What do you say?
-I don't say anything.
(Sheldon:)I merely offer you a facial expression
that suggests you've gone insane.
(Raj:)-I don't get it. You had a great time.
-Yes, exactly. I had a great time.
(Sheldon:)That's done.
I've moved on to other things.
(Sheldon:)For example, after I learn Finnish,
I'm not going to learn Finnish again.
(Raj:)Please, Sheldon.
(Raj:)I'm a lost Indian boy far from home...
(Raj:)...and I want a girlfriend,
and I want her to be Abby...
(Raj:)...and she'll only come
if she can bring Martha.
(Sheldon:)I highly doubt
there is any argument you can make...
(Sheldon:)...threat you might levy,
rhetorical strategy, plea, invocation...
...supplication or "vetoomus"
that you can employ...
(Sheldon:)...that would convince me
to reconsider.
(Raj:)My Incredible Hulk hands
signed by Stan Lee.